

JOHN GLENDENING, PMP Current Position: Senior Analyst

EDUCATION/CERTIFICATION

M.B.A., University of Kansas, 2011 B.S., Political Science, University of Kansas, 2005 Project Management Professional (PMP), 2014 Certified Fraud Examiner (CFE), 2015

SECURITY CLEARANCE

Secret Clearance, 06/2012

EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

Mr. Glendening was recently a Senior Analyst with Kearney & Company, P.C. (Kearney) with more than six years of professional experience, including one and a half years of Department of Defense (DoD) experience. Mr. Glendening's experience includes analyzing critical data elements, managing complex databases, and providing project management support for DoD. Mr. Glendening is experienced coordinating and facilitating meetings, preparing briefings, drafting meeting minutes, and briefing key Government personnel as required. Additionally, during his time providing support to the United States Air Force (AF), he coordinated external audit/visits with AF bases ahead of critical internal control/audit testing. Mr. Glendening is very outgoing and adapts easily to any environment, and his organization skills allow him to work great under pressure. Representative experience appears below.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Navy—Financial Improvement
Plan/Financial Improvement Audit
Readiness (FIP/FIAR)— Senior Analyst 11/2015 to 06/28/2017
Contractor Support for Audit
Functions

• As a Senior Analyst, Mr. Glendening served as a team member on the Department of Navy (Navy) Financial Improvement Plan (FIP) consulting engagement (subcontracting for Booz Allen Hamilton) assisting the CNRF. The primary focus of the engagement was to review and improve internal controls, processes, and policies in place at CNRF with the ultimate goal of attaining audit readiness. Mr. Glendening was responsible for assisting with the

Reimbursable Work Orders - Performer and Grantor (RWO-P&G), Military Standard Requisitioning and Issue Procedures (MILSTRIP), Contracts and Vendor Pay (C-VP), and Civilian Pay (CIV PAY) segments. Mr. Glendening also prepared the weekly team meeting updates to help keep a record of past, current, and future project endeavors.

USDA NRCS—Accounting Operations Data Analyst 10/2014 to 06/28/2017

 As a Data Analyst and member of the Accounting Operations team, Mr. Glendening worked on various data analysis projects for NRCS operations. It was his duty to provide new database systems to help speed up operations and simplify NRCS tasks. Mr. Glendening helped with variance analysis for certain financial operations. Mr. Glendening also helped to verify content and edit requests for NRCS conferences and training events.

NSF Data Analyst Senior Analyst 11/2016 to 06/28/2017

• As a Data Analyst and member of the NSF audit team, Mr. Glendening worked with collected data to reconcile with master files and analyze for correctness. It was his duty to provide the NSF audit team with reports developed using ACL analytics software.

DoD JIEDDO—IR Support for MIC and Audit Functions

Audit Liaison 05/2013 to 02/2014

• As an Audit Liaison with Kearney and member of the Managers' Internal Control (MIC) for the Joint Improvised Explosive Device Defeat Organization's (JIEDDO) Internal Review (IR), Mr. Glendening worked directly with the Chief of IR. His duties ranged from preparing slide presentations for status updates to JIEDDO's Director or Chief of Staff, aiding MIC with reviewing and documenting processes, reviewing weekly Director's Priorities for pertinent IR information, and assisting with necessary daily administrative functions. Mr. Glendening also was responsible for maintaining In-Processing and Out-Processing procedures for all IR team members.

AOUSC—Cyclical and Financial Audits of the U.S. Courts

Data Miner 04/2013 to 06/28/2017

• Mr. Glendening took over responsibilities as the Data Miner for Kearney supporting the Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts (AOUSC). Mr. Glendening was responsible for producing data mining reports for the U.S. Courts project, providing sample selections to the audit teams, creating new requested reports for audits, tracking the status of current requests, enhancing the way the reports are created, updating and maintaining a manual, and other assigned activities. Mr. Glendening's responsibilities included collecting and standardizing data from databases, performing financial and data analyses, and ensuring timeliness of deliverables. The complexity of the data analysis required the use of Microsoft (MS) Access, IDEA® Data Analysis Software, MS Excel, and more advanced database programming applications.

HUD— Single Family Acquired Asset Management System (SAMS) Staff Accountant 08/2012 to 11/2012 Transaction Processing As a Staff Accountant with Kearney, Mr. Glendening assisted with daily operations at the
Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD). Mr. Glendening was responsible
for ensuring that daily operations were done in a timely and efficient manner and met
required deadlines. He assisted in editing and processing mortgage loan paperwork,
contacting mortgage loan companies, and ensuring daily records were updated.

AF—FIP/FIAR Support Staff Accountant 03/2012 to 08/2012

• As a Staff Accountant with Kearney and member of the Project Management Office on the Financial Improvement Plan (FIP)/Financial Improvement Audit Readiness (FIAR) team, Mr. Glendening worked directly with the AF Audit Readiness Director. His duties ranged from facilitating meetings, managing calendar requirements, and performing administrative tasks such as reviewing reporting requirements to ensure proper documentation processes were being followed. Mr. Glendening was in charge of setting up and overseeing the execution of the bimonthly Executive Steering Committee meetings and bimonthly Integrated Process Team meetings. Mr. Glendening documented meeting presentations, interactions, and questions. He also was in charge of preparing meeting presentations in accordance with AF standards. On occasion, Mr. Glendening was asked to analyze assessable unit team metrics, look for consistencies and errors, and attend command-level meetings representing the Audit Readiness directorate. Sporadic duties included analyzing and editing documents for the Audit Readiness Director and helping assessable unit managers with scheduling.

Titan Energy Pulling Unit Supervisor 06/2011 to 02/2012

• As a Pulling Unit Supervisor at Titan Energy, Mr. Glendening managed a Titan Energy labor staff of seven and oversaw outside contractor performance on down-hole remedial/completion work and access road construction. He negotiated with landowners concerning acquisition of new leases and oil production rights and ensured production level of wells met consistent output-to-profit specifications (~~\$7K/day). Mr. Glendening traveled to operating locations and gauged well output, tank capacity, and equipment/operational status. He also gauged and adjusted water and nitrogen balance levels for maximum well output efficiency and operational safety. Mr. Glendening assisted in pumping unit maintenance, including bimonthly joint and motor greasing, and belt and bearings repair/replacement. He evaluated tank and well integrity and repaired leaks in tanks, vessels, oil lines, and water injection lines and assessed and repaired underground or above-ground 480-volt electric line short circuits.

University of Kansas, Jayhawk Consulting Project Coordinator 01/2011 to 05/2011

• Mr. Glendening served as the Project Coordinator of Jayhawk Consulting at the University of Kansas. He led five consultants in ad hoc profit erosion analysis for Allen Press and scheduled and conducted individual meetings with all team members to ensure deadlines were met and the project timetable remained viable. Mr. Glendening assisted in defining the role of each primary Allen Press service to better target and acquire customers from both a strategic and financial resource standpoint. He authored a team analysis results and recommendations briefing to present team findings and recommendations to Allen Press executives. This employment opportunity was part of the Masters of Business Administration (MBA) capstone course.

Wal-Mart Team Lead 03/2009 to 08/2010

As a Team Lead of the Produce Department at Wal-Mart, Mr. Glendening oversaw the duties
and performance of 10 associates. He was responsible for on-the-job training and coaching
of associates and acted as front-line customer service representative for customers needing
assistance. Mr. Glendening developed superior conflict resolution skills dealing with
dissatisfied customers and adapted to roles and responsibilities as requested, working
whenever and wherever there was a need across all departments.

Waddell & Reed Financial Advisor 08/2005 to 12/2008

• Mr. Glendening was a Financial Advisor at Waddell & Reed. During this time, he built an investment business from scratch. He marketed services to prospective investors and developed clientele through presentations and strong word-of-mouth recommendations. Mr. Glendening managed retirement portfolios for 20 clients with an aggregate net worth of \$3.2M and received exceptional performance evaluations from supervisors and clients. He provided insurance advice to clients and enhanced knowledge base and skill set by acquiring Series 6, 7, 63, and 66 licensures. Mr. Glendening earned the CFMC designation from College for Financial Planning.

COMPUTER/OTHER TECHNICAL SKILLS

Mr. Glendening is proficient in MS Office Suite and IDEA Data Analysis Software

MEMBERSHIPS AND AFFILIATIONS

N/A

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Kearney & Company Senior Analyst 04/2012 to 06/28/2017

Titan Energy Pulling Unit Supervisor 06/2011 to 03/2012

University of Kansas Project Coordinator 01/2011 to 05/2011

Wal-Mart Team Lead 03/2009 to 08/2010

Waddell & Reed Financial Advisor 08/2005 to 12/2008

 $\textit{The information contained on this page is proprietary and confidential and cannot be \textit{reproduced without Kearney \& Company's consent.} \\$